How much does it help you already having
that familiarity with I think he
counting on you not only to be a
playmaker but to be somebody that can
kind of lead people till they understand
the offense fully too.
>> Um I mean I think it's a big part um
being in the offense for four years. Um,
obviously I think he probably changed up
some stuff, you know, just being able to
sit back and reflect. But, um,
obviously, yeah, I'm going to be a big
part in helping the guys and I'm going
to, um, kind of take that initiative to
try and help and do as much as I can to
make sure that everybody's, um, getting
to know the offense. So, I'm just going
to try and do my best with that.
>> TD, go ahead.
And as far as that familiarity and
playing in that slot position, like how
much have you seen that offense rely so
much on the slot as far as the targets?
Like you look, 280 targets in the last
uh uh two years for you, 41% for for
first downs. So, how has that worked for
you?
>> Um, you know, a lot of games the Daves
can just find that matchup and being
able to um, you know, get open on those
option routes and stuff like that. feel
like it's kind of a big part of the
offense and you know being able to get
the ball out quick and um you know
finding zones and finding just little
little areas to get open. So just feel
like I've kind of done that pretty well
the past two years and kind of expanded
more on that this past year and just
being able to expand the zones a little
bit more just by going down the field
too. So
>> Wale
for you to play with Cam Ward.
Oh my
my dog.
>> Good.
>> I appreciate you. But no, I say, you
know, I'm ready to play with you. That's
part of the reason I came.
>> All right, Buck, go ahead.
>> Yeah, Wale. Uh, Buck Rising 1045. Um,
how would you describe Brian Dable as a
coach after working with him for the
last couple years? Um, I would say
creative. Um,
definitely intense. Um, I mean, he's
definitely he's going to get on you
whenever things aren't going right and
cuz obviously he just wants us to be the
best offense that we can be, but um,
it's coming it's all coming from a good
place that, you know, he wants us to be
the best and um, he wants to get this
thing right.
Steve
>> Juan Dale, Steve Layman from News
Channel 5 in Nashville. At the risk of
Cam still being on there, what what did
you see uh from him from afar and and
what is exciting about playing with a
young talented quarterback as your QB?
>> Yeah, I mean obviously, you know, if you
just watch the watch the tape, you know,
just him being able to create plays
outside of the pocket, that's obviously
that's what really stands out about last
year. and um you know just being that
valuable target just always being able
to be um open for a guy um and you know
they they sold me that they needed um
needed somebody like that. So that was
really kind of what got me and um you
know just being able to grow with a
young quarterback like that and just
being able to see um where he he can get
to.
>> Chris PK then Nick. Hey, Juan Dale.
Chris Harris at WSMV4 here. For the
folks that may not know, uh, how would
you describe your strengths as a
receiver to the Titans fan base?
>> Um, you know, I would say reliable. Um,
you know, just always, let's say, open
and then, um, you know, just explosive,
just always trying to make plays, too.
So,
>> hi Wanda. Paul Kuharski. Uh, been with
the team since 96. Have my own website.
Um, I know people really pigeon hole you
as a slot guy.
>> I know you were outside like 43% of the
time last year and that Brian runs a lot
of too tight. Um, that that's becoming
more popular. Tell us about what you can
do outside and how much you expect to be
outside.
>> Um, yeah, I mean I I expect to play
outside. Um, you know, I felt like I did
it pretty well this past year and um,
you know, just gotten more and more
confidence each and every time that I
was out there. um you know just being
more of a slot only my previous three
years and um I had done it in college
but you know obviously had had some time
off so it it took a little bit to get
used to but um definitely you know
training more for playing on the outside
and doing certain things like that for
the for the season. So
>> how different are the two jobs? Um
they're different in their own ways, but
similar at the same time, too, you know.
Um you know, just kind of depending on
the alignment and exactly where you are
on the outside. Like a lot of times I'm
not just lined up by myself on the
outside, so I can always sometimes still
treat it like the slot and um use some
of the same releases and um the same
setup. So um you know, just a couple
different routes that you can run from
out there.
>> Hey, Wale Nick Susan Tennessee
newspaper. Um, seems like every single
person in the NFL predicted you would
come to the Titans through free.
>> Was there ever any thought for you for
any other team? Were the Titans the only
team on your radar? And was there any
other reason besides Dable or was it
just simply you were going to go where
he was?
>> Um, no. It wasn't just going where he
was. There's a lot of factors into it.
You know, I'm from Kentucky and that's
closer to home for me and um, you know,
just a place that I just felt like was
kind of a perfect fit for me. It was
just kind of a new staff, knew
everything. Um, obviously Dave's being
there was an added bonus, but um, yeah,
I mean, obviously thought about going
back, going back to New York and, um,
there's some other some other teams on
on the table, but ultimately it was kind
of Tennessee or New York really at the
end of the day. So,
>> Corey TD, then Terry,
>> hey Wal, this is Cory Curtis from News 2
in Nashville. Obviously, you had massive
volume the last two years with almost 10
targets per game and 185 receptions. Are
you expecting that kind of volume again
with the Titans?
>> Um, I'm not going to I don't want to
want to put a number on how many targets
or the volume or anything like that. At
the end of the day, um, just going out
there trying to get open for Cam and um,
you know, the targets will come. So
that's that's at the end of the day my
job is to go out there and get open and
um just do my job. So
>> well D you you mentioned those choice
routes and obviously you know when
you're in the slot that's going to be
critical with Cam Ward. You've played
with what six quarterbacks over the last
two years and all the production. What's
the key? How do you approach getting on
that same page to where you and Cam are
looking at things through the same
perspective, the same eyes? I mean, I
would say it's just a lot of watching
watching tape and um you know, and then
going out there and doing it. You know,
it's takes a lot of practice and um a
lot of time that's not seen at practice
that you got to work on those type of
routes and work on those scenarios and
um you know, just always talking to him,
just asking him, was this how you want
this? This how you want that? Like, is
this indicator right? And um whatever it
is to give him the right thing going on
in his mind um to be able to put the
ball where it needs to be. Juan
Dale, uh, you played, uh, college ball
at Kentucky, obviously with Will Levis.
Uh, how much have you kept in touch
with, uh, Will and, uh, did he say
anything to you about you coming here
and, uh, kind of what's kind of been
that frame of mind that if you talked to
him as far as his comeback?
>> Yeah. Um, yeah, I talked to him. I said,
we go to the derby every year together,
so we're always at least seeing each
other once a year. Um but yeah, he hit
me up whenever he um saw the news that I
was going to be a Titan and um obviously
don't know exactly what the future holds
and everything like that, but um excited
to be teammates with him as of right
now. So,
>> okay, Wendell, I think that's about it.
I appreciate your time. Yes,
>> sir. Thank you.
>> Nice to meet you. We look forward to
working with you.
>> Yep. Thank you.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Yep. players, you know, have said that.
But in your perspective, what is the
Robert Salah advantage, the attraction
and playing for him?
>> I mean, uh, outside of, you know, I'll
touch on his character and kind of what
he brings, you know, as a coach day in
day out, but kind of first things first,
I mean, this defense, if you're a D
lineman, you're not playing this style
defense. Um, I mean, just look to him
cuz it it is addicting and and it is
very violent and uh you will wreak
havoc. But like I said, um his character
and how he goes about coaching, he's the
same guy every day. Um he does not he
does not um he does not uh give in on
his standard and what he has for
everybody and for the team. So I just a
very consistent uh messenger in that
aspect. And um yeah, I just like
everything he comes with, everything
he's about. Uh, I told him as soon as I
got traded, just just point out the wall
and I'll run through it.
>> Hey, Germaine. Julian Minzone, News 2
here in Nashville. Uh, welcome. Um, you
tweeted you went one for one on the
first wave of recruiting in free agency.
Uh, how much is that is kind of an
extension of your leadership on the
field? And, um, is the recruiting hat
still off?
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, um, I just JFM is is
is definitely a brother for life and and
as soon as I found out that that was
kind of a possibility, um, I had to do
everything in my power to make it
happen, I'm sure he was annoyed at all
the phone calls and texts and whatnot,
but um, hey, it ended up working out
and, um, I'm just glad to have that guy
back on the same D line as me and and I
know everything he brings on and off the
field, so I'm super excited. Um, and in
terms of leadership, uh, I just I mean,
you got to earn everything everything
you got. So, uh, we'll see how that
goes. But, um, but yeah, that's just
kind of how I look at that.
>> Hey, Germaine, mix us at the
Tennesseeian here in town. Um, when you
look back on those Jets years with
solid, obviously great defenses and the
team results maybe didn't always catch
up there. What do you guys need to do to
carry over that defensive performance
and kind of what extra needs to be done
to translate good defenses into good
playoff teams?
>> Yeah, I mean it's a the thing about
football is the the greatest team sport
on the face of the earth. So, uh it
doesn't matter if you have a top five,
top two defense. Um, you know, all
phases of a football team need to need
to do their part, pull their weight and
and and that's that's kind of how the
great teams get get the ultimate job
done and winning a Super Bowl and and
going far in the in the playoffs and
whatnot. So, um, yeah, we just
everybody's got to understand that we
all have to pull our own weight and and
the standard is the standard and and uh
there's no exception. So, I mean, I've
talked with Cam and and some of the guys
on the offense and I'm super excited to
work with him. He's got a chip on his
shoulder. got fire with him and and uh
yeah that I'm just I'm just excited to
be here and uh and just see see what
this group can turn into.
Germaine uh Terry McCormack, Main Street
Nashville and Titaninsider.com.
Uh this is your be your second year
coming back from the Achilles injury.
How how long did it take you last year
to start feeling like yourself again?
And now, do you feel like with another
full year beyond the injury, you feel
like you're back to your old self
completely?
>> Yeah. Um, I'd say somewhere around the
Ravens game, um, is when I was like,
"Okay, I feel like I feel like me
again." You know, cuz I, you know, I
used to just think I was invincible. I'd
never been hurt in my life. And, uh,
I've always played like, you know, 70 to
90% of snaps, you know, all the high
school, college, NFL. And, um, yeah, I
just always thought I was invincible.
and then you know that kind of fluke
happened. Um and uh and yeah, so it does
have some sort of some sort of lay on
your mind in terms of uh just being
weary and stuff like that, but you know,
this game is not about that. You can't
play it like that. So, as soon as I uh
as soon as I just felt comfortable and
and you know, the doctors and everybody
said I was good to go, I just kind of,
you know, full pedal to the to the
metal, didn't look back. Um, but but
yes, I'm super excited to get this off
seasonason, a full uh offseason under my
belt where I'm not just rehabbing, you
know, a ankle or a calf and and I get to
really just hone my craft again and and
u it's all the more it makes all the
more difference that I'm back in I'm
back in a system where um you know they
tell you to just go ruin offense's day
and it's as simple as that. I mean,
there's more nuances to it, but you
know, when you can when you can tell a a
defensive line to kind of just go about
their business like that, a lot of good
things happen. So, I'm excited to to to
be back in that.
>> Germaine Terresa Walker with the
Associated Press. Uh, you mentioned
Salah and and JFM and Cam Ward. Uh, the
idea of playing on a defensive front
with Jeff Simmons. Uh, how exciting is
that to you and and the possibilities of
what this line group can do together?
>> I can't put it into words. I I spoke to
Jeff when I was out there, you know,
signing and whatnot and and and I was we
were just talking about how excited we
are and and obviously I've seen what
he's done and and and you meet him and
the kind of guy he is off the field,
it's just uh you know, it just makes it
all the better cuz you when you get to
go to work with good people and uh those
good people are also uh able to ruin the
offenses day single-handedly, you know,
that's that's a good thing. So, um,
yeah, I'm just great to blessed to
really, um, be in that position and be
able to play next to him. JFM, you know,
Fei is a guy I think will be very
amazing in this system. Um, so yeah, I'm
just again, I can't put it into words.
I'm excited to to see to see where what
this group brings us.
>> What's up, Germaine? Buck Rising with
1045 here in town. Um, you you mentioned
obviously Salin, what that defense lets
you guys do uh up front, but he's going
to call plays here in Tennessee. I know
that's different from what he did in New
York. What what do you think that will
help unlock with the defense and and how
adv advantageous do you think he is as a
football mind?
>> I mean, just kind of look what he did um
with Sam Fran when some of his best guys
went down. you know, those guys were
still a still a still to be reckoned
with with that defense. So, um, just
that that's kind of all I have to say
about it. When when you got your best
players on defense go down and you're
still kind of giving the offense hell
and trying to get past you, it's uh, you
know, it's a pretty good sign and um,
and yeah, I'm just excited to be a part
of that.
>> Hey, Jermaine. Cory Curtis here with
News 2. You talked about that pass rush.
How much of this defense is predicated
on getting pressure with four and with
JFM and Jeff? H how set do you think you
guys are to do that?
>> Very set. Very set. Um I'm not worried
about that in the slightest. And uh the
thing about this defense is it it
thrives. It very much so lives on the
front four getting home or affecting the
quarterback in some form or fashion. Um,
so yeah, if you don't have a front four,
that can affect the quarterback. Um, you
know, there's gonna be a lot of blitzes
going on and whatnot. So, coach very
much emphasizes just if if the if if the
quarterback's holding the ball
effectively for longer than 3 seconds, 4
seconds, you guys are you guys are dead
wrong. Sir,
>> with that front with that front four
being relied upon a lot of versatility
there, how much of an advantage, you
know, does it give you guys to have so
many interchangeable parts, you know,
whereas some play inside, outside, all
the multiple techniques and everything?
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't know if you guys
are familiar with um his style of
defensive line, but we rotate. Um, so
we're always fresh out there. Um, so
there's just always gonna be fresh legs
out there and and uh always gonna be
able to get to the quarterback because
like you said, you asked how important
that was. Uh, it's as important as as
you can believe. So if if there's even a
hint of fatigue in any of the guys, you
know, we're rolling and uh we're getting
fresh legs out there. We're going to
continue to affect the quarterback.
>> Germaine, what was it like for you last
Monday watching all of the signings come
in? I know you'd been with the Titans
for a couple of weeks before then, so
seeing five, six, seven people sign all
at once. Just kind of what was your
reaction to how the team was building?
>> Yeah, I mean, I was I wasn't officially
with the Titans until, you know,
everybody else, you know, for the rules.
But, uh, it was awesome cuz I just keep
seeing all my old teammates being my
teammates again. Um, and like I said,
I'm just blessed. This is a blessing
from God. I I I can't put into words
because I mean, I've said this in
another interview, how many guys are
lucky enough to to go to a different
team that is in a city they've already
been looking to move to, that has a head
coach that that drafted him, you know,
has a defensive line coach that that
kind of like built him up to be who he
is, running a scheme that he's very
effective in and fell in love with. So,
I I have zero complaints on this end.
Uh, I have no words to ex to say how
excited I am. Um, so I'm just I'm just
ready to get to work and uh and just
have have a great have a great year to
be honest.
>> Okay, Germaine, I think that'll do it.
Really appreciate your time today.
>> Watched a lot of your film last year.
There was a a big uptick in in playing
in the nickel as opposed to left corner
the year before. What was behind that?
How do you project yourself playing with
with this Titans team? And what is it
that excites you about Robert Salah?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, my my rookie year, I
came into a great situation. Um, loaded,
I'd say probably one of the best loaded
defensive back rooms. Um, my opportunity
came with uh just injuries. Um, and so
played corner obviously my rookie year
and then my second year. Um, you know,
just a situation, man, where, you know,
we got to get the best guys on the
field. Um, competed with my guy Paul and
Adbo who's with New York now as for the
CB2 job. Um, didn't get that, which was
okay cuz I know that, you know, they
needed me on the field as well. So, they
end up moving me into the slot. Never
played it. Um, had a lot of learn learn
learning curves with it. Learned a lot.
Um, and then I just kind of uh stayed
there for a little bit. And then when
Coach Staley came um to New Orleans,
just using me in both both situations,
right, inside outside uh seeing my value
that I still had on the outside um and
allowing me to play there and uh do what
I can do best. Um and then now coming
into to Tennessee, man, I see myself um
really just playing on the outside um
you know, having a little bit of
conversation with coach and things like
that since I got in the building. Um, I
think my role is kind of clear. Um, but
if need be and if game plan situations
need me to slide back into the slot,
then you know, I'm obviously I've played
there, so I'll be comfortable if need to
be.
>> Julian Menson, News 2 here in Nashville.
Welcome, Alante. Um, what's it like to
be home, man? And and also is that
request for uh tickets uh from the
family and friends, is that already
pretty long?
>> Uh, it's awesome, man. Um, I'm glad to
be back. Um, and I'm a family guy and
so, uh, just glad to be around them. And
as far as the tickets go, um, not yet.
Um, but and I know that that they're
coming. Um, I've just been getting a lot
of congratulations and welcome home and
even welcome home congratulations from
people I haven't I never even heard from
when I got drafted to New Orleans. So,
ticket list might be long, but the
actual tickets given will be short.
Alante Terresa Walker with the
Associated Press. Uh, welcome to town or
back to town uh, in the state. What as
you hit free agency, what was the
biggest selling points as you were
looking at the Titans? Was it Salah as
the new coach? Was it Jeff Simmons being
on that front line? What was it that uh,
made this the choice for you?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, Coach Salah is
somebody I've always wanted to to play
for. I think when you when you play in
this league for um a long time,
obviously I haven't been here in a long
time, but I've played long enough to to
hear about and see a lot of defensive
game uh schemes, see a lot of defensive
coordinators, um watch a lot of film,
watch a lot of tape, and you know, Coach
Sal is just one of those names and and
coaches that you you see what they've
done, you see, uh the success that he's
had as a as a coordinator. Um and you
just want to play for him, right? Um, I
kind of talked about it before, you
know, DJ Reed and Sauce over there with
the Jets with him, uh, the improvements
and just the success rate that those
guys had. Um, and then, you know, you
look at Lenor in San Francisco and just
him playing that inside outside before
Coach Holl got there and then once Coach
Holl got there, moved him to just
playing outside and then seeing how well
he played there. Um, so just that alone,
I'm like, man, like I've always wanted
to play for him. And then when Tennessee
hired him, I was like, wow, I can go
back home. um like this is an
opportunity. It's a team that needs
corners. Um and I think it would just
fit. Um it felt really good last year
when when New Orleans came and we played
played in Nashville. Uh just to see my
family, my friends, and just kind of
play in front of the home crowd. And
it's crazy. It just kind of all just
circled itself back around. Um a lot of
options, a lot of dissecting, a lot of
praying, a lot of tough decisions that
needed to be made. Um but I think
ultimately I ended up exactly where I
needed to be. And I'm super super super
excited uh to really just get started.
>> Latte. Uh Terry McCormack uh Main Street
Nashville and Titan Insider.com. Uh you
talked about them needing quarterbacks
here. That's pretty barren room until
they signed you and Cordell and a couple
of other guys. Uh how do you see
yourself kind of having to develop into
a leader of that room right away? uh
even though you're the new guy, but
being maybe the most veteran of the
group.
>> Yeah, I think it's um natural I should
say. Um I've always felt like I was a
naturalb born leader. Um you know, I had
opportunity to lead a really good DB
room as I got older. Um there in
Knoxville with with the Tennessee
Volunteers and I learned a whole lot um
just being in New Orleans as as a as a
young pup. And like I said, I had a
loaded DB room in New Orleans with
Marshon Latimore, Bradley Roby, John
Chanty Gardner Johnson, Tyron Matthew,
PJ Williams. Like I had a lot of great
veteran guys who's had a lot of success
in this league. And just watching those
guys lead that room there. Um and then
as it slowly got to being my turn to
lead the room um like this past season
in New Orleans, um it it felt fine. It
felt normal. It didn't feel like any
pressure. I didn't feel like I wasn't
ready for the moment. Um, and just, you
know, coming to n coming to Nashville
and, you know, getting to sign my
paperwork and things like that and just
kind of move around the facility, um, I
already feel like I'm at home again. And
so, I think just leading those guys, um,
you know, by example first, um, and then
vocally second, I think will be the best
traits and the best ways to lead this
room and just bring a lot of swag, man,
to this defense, to the quarterback
room. And, um, I think it's going to
it's going to come naturally and and I
think everyone's going to enjoy, uh, the
product.
Paul, go ahead.
>> Hey, Alante. Paul Kuherski, Paul
Kuherski.com. Nice to meet you. Um, I
know the numbers that are out there uh
by outside analytics aren't always dead
on, but uh they've got you giving up
eight touchdowns last year, 13 the last
two years. How do you feel about um what
you've done in terms of keeping people
out of the end zones end zone and and uh
how much do you maybe need to get better
at that element?
>> Great question. Um
I think
what what what first and foremost I
think you have to think about schemes.
You have to understand responsibilities.
Um, I've obviously seen those those
numbers myself and I've went back and
looked at film myself and I've ran over
every single defensive call that we've
had where touchdowns were scored and
it's like uh eight touchdowns this past
season is is is crazy. Um, but if that's
what people see on film and if people
feel like those are my responsibilities
and that is what it is. I mean, playing
the position that I play, uh, that can
happen. But, you know, at the end of the
day, man, just locking in on on my job
and what I can do to help this team and
to help this secondary um is all that I
care about. I mean, wins and losses is
the most important thing here. Um, and I
think, you know, when we do things as a
team and we win as a team, all the
individual stuff, it is what it is. And
so, um, I think I can't really sit here
and say, I got to do this better, do
that better, do this better, do that
better. I think ultimately just, uh,
continue just to do my job and get
better as a player every single day, get
better as a teammate every single day.
Um, and then come Sundays, just go out
there and just put, you know, my best
foot forward.
>> Steve Layman from News Channel 5 here in
Nashville. Welcome home. I'm curious,
how much did you watch the Titans
growing up and now with this
opportunity? They unveiled the new
uniforms last week, new stadiums on the
way in a year, new coaching staff, new
opportunity for you. How much do you
embrace the chance to be a part of a
new, hopefully very successful era here
with the Titans? I embrace it a lot. Um
it's it's it's
crazy because the new uniforms, they're
sick. Like I love them. And then like
you talk about the new stadium being
here in a year. Um you know, new
coaching staff. Um
is awesome. But you know, I never really
watched um Tennessee much. My my mom and
my aunt, you know, they were big Chris
Johnson fans, so they would watch the
games. Um, and I was just reminded, it's
crazy, I even forgot, but in high school
I was like the Tennessee player of the
week or something like that. And I know
the Titans, I don't know if they still
do it, but they kind of invited those
guys to the games and then they kind of
like present them this trophy and they
put them on the screen like the
Tennessee player of the week or
whatever. Um, so that was probably my
first game I ever came to. Um, and then
I think my junior year, senior year of
high school was my second game. Um, but
never really paid too much close of
attention to the Titans. Um, but you
know, I'm here now and and I've watched
them. I've played them the past I played
them twice since being in New Orleans.
So, um, you know, I'm here now. I'm
ready to get this thing going and do it
for, you know, the home team.
>> Volante. Chris Harris at WSMV. I'm
curious what you talked about things
that you maybe need to get better on.
What do you feel you do the best right
now? And also uh what what's the
challenge of joining a room now that's
basically being rebuilt?
>> Yeah, I think uh you know some of the
best things that I bring to the game,
man, is my press man. Uh playing
man-to-man defense. Uh physicality. I
think I'm super physical. Um I think uh
you know, I think I tackle well. I think
times that I might try to go and blow up
a play or I don't come to balance will
be areas that I can improve on, but the
want to um to tackle is there. Um no
fear or anything like that. And uh but
my press man, my my my confidence, my my
toughness, my physicality
um and my swagger uh would be the things
that I I feel like I bring to the table
and I do best. Um and what was the
second part of your question?
>> Yeah, just stepping into a room that's
being rebuilt.
>> Yeah. Um, I think I've been a part of a
couple rebuilds my since I've played
football. You know, uh, you know, I come
to the University of Tennessee under a
new head coach, no coaches really hired
yet, right? And, um, figure that part
out and then I go into my senior year
where I had opportunities with the
transfer portal to go, you know,
anywhere else I wanted to go. Um, but I
ended up deciding to stay with a whole
new coaching staff, uh, new guys coming
into the room. Um, and then, you know,
getting into the NFL and changing new
positions and trying to learn and
understand that. So, I think I've been
around a lot of change. I feel like God
has put me through a lot of obstacles to
overcome and I feel like I've I've
embraced them and I've learned through
those and grew through those that has
prepared me for this exact moment. Um,
so I'm super excited to meet the rest of
the corners. I'm super excited to meet,
you know, the rest of the DBs and learn
them and them learn me and um, you know,
we we figure out, you know, what are we
going to do um to make sure that we take
this defense to the next level?
>> Last one. Cory.
>> Hey, Elante. Cory Curtis, News 2 in
Nashville. You you said the new uniforms
were sick. What do you like about him?
And is it true that John Franklin Myers
looks better in that uniform than than
anyone else on the team?
um the John Franklin Myers when I I
wouldn't put any votes on any of that
yet. I think I'm gonna be the cleanest
guy in the uniform. Um but um
uh what I love about the uniforms, I
like I love the colors. Um I I love the
new logo. Um you know, I'm only 27, so
some people might hate me for saying
that, but uh you know um the logo is
pretty sick and and I just love the
colors. I love the white helmet. I love
the white face mask. um the little bits
of red in there. You know, red being one
of my favorite colors, so definitely
have to add some red to my to my swag
for the season. Uh but I think, you
know, I just really like how it's kind
of straight to the point. Um it's not
too much going on. Um but it's clean,
it's smooth, the blue is is dope. I kind
of seen something where somebody wanted
to see blue on blue. Um so hopefully we
can get that going for a game or two uh
just to kind of fill it out. But yeah.
>> All right, Alante, I think that'll do
it. I appreciate your time.
>> Cool. Appreciate you.
>> All right.
>> Thanks a lot.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank Thank you.
>> Yo, what's up, man? Terron Davenport,
ESPN. Wanted to ask you about Robert
Salah and what was it that made you want
to come back here so much? And then
looking at your usage from with him and
then with the Broncos. You know, you
played a lot more inside with the
Broncos. Is that something you see
yourself doing here alongside Jeffrey
Simmons or what do you think the plan
will be?
>> Uh, shoot. I mean, Coach Solid is, I
mean, just, you know, one of the best
coaches I've had. Uh, I think he's a
leader of men. I think that he
understands football. He understands
from a player perspective, you know, how
to relate to players. I think that when
um you get a group of guys together, um
it takes a special type of guy to be
able to lead a group of men and of of
different age groups. And he does a
great job of doing it. I think that uh
man, he's so smart. I love the defense
and I love the people that he puts in
place for us. And uh I'd say as far as
my role, I mean, you know, I think my
superpower is that I can I can kind of
play every position in that um he's
going to utilize me to be able to do
that. And I I'll say that uh he did it
at the Jets. I was able to play outside
and inside. Um, at the Broncos, I played
a little more inside, which, um, you
know, I wasn't exactly a fan of when I
got there, but, uh, grew to love it,
grew to understand it so much, and I
think it'll help me going forward when,
uh, I do kind of transition back to kind
of doing both again.
>> Nick Sus.
>> Hey, John. Nick Sus at the Tennessee
here. Um, not just you, obviously, a lot
of people coming from that Jets team to
to join this squad. those weren't
necessarily playoff teams. Kind of what
gives you the confidence that reuniting
all these pieces, doing things the way
you guys did it there can actually spark
something second try in Nashville.
>> Yeah, I think that uh I mean again I
believe in coal. I believe in you know
the experience. I believe that
experience is the biggest teacher and um
he was able to go through that process
be a head coach. He was able to see and
correct his mistakes. he was able to go
back to be a defense coordinator for a
year and kind of again reperfect that.
Now he's going to call plays u for the
Titans and I think uh you know he put
the right coach staff in play uh there's
a lot of experience in place and uh man
I'm extremely confident with what we
got. I'm extremely confident in the
players we got um already on the team
and through free agency and I know the
plan for the draft is going to be
amazing.
Paul, you want to go next?
>> Hi, John. Paul Kuherski. I've got my own
website. I've been covering the team
since Houston. Um, why not just for you,
but but for all of these guys that
they've added uh up front, almost
everybody can bounce around inside,
outside, and I know Robert wants to
bring guys in waves. Why is it so
important that you have all of these
pieces that can go inside and outside?
What kind of problems do you envision
you guys causing with that?
>> I I think the beautiful part about what
he does is that um he never puts anybody
in the box. And that's um co that's
white cotton. That's even assistant D
line coach um Janzel um Gus man. I think
u very highly of those guys. I I think
that the people they put there they put
there for a reason. They understand that
none of us are selfish people. We'll
play any position and you know the best
part of it is you know I can go outside,
Jay can go inside, Sally can go inside.
I mean Jeff can go outside, inside
everybody can do it at all and so you
know you can kind of mess with
protections. You can kind of dictate how
you want uh the slide to go and that's
the beautiful part of what he does is
able to get us one-on- ones, put us on
mismatches um every game and I think
that uh you guys will see that soon.
Terry, go ahead.
>> Terry McCormack, Main Street Nashville
and Titansider.com.
Uh, John, what's been your take of
Jeffrey Simmons watching from afar and
how do you feel like the two of you can
complement each other playing alongside
on the same line?
>> Yeah. Uh, man, I've been a fan of Jeff.
I think uh you watch enough football,
you all I do is watch tape by watch
actually breaks down offensive lineman
when they're rushing and he does a great
job. He uses power. He's able to use
speed, quickness, and I look at that, I
kind of use some of that. But Jeff is
also a freaking nature. And I think that
some of the stuff he does um most can't
can't mimic and you kind of understand
what he's doing from a football
perspective and utilize what you can
while you're playing. But um I think as
good as he is, uh man, I'm going one-on
ones on the opposite side of him. if he
gets a slide, um I know that um there's
going to be a time where they have to
slide to me and he's going to get a
chance to win his one-on- ones. And I
know he will. And I think the beautiful
part of it is whether I'm outside or
inside, we can play together and um play
off of one another.
>> Julian, then Corey.
>> Hey, John. Julian Min channel 2 here in
Nashville. Welcome to Music City, by the
way. Um, Germaine Johnson was very
public about uh his recruiting pitch for
you. What did you make of that and how
much did that pitch uh maybe influence
your decision to uh sign with the
Titans?
>> Yeah, Germaine is the character and uh I
mean I seen him as a rookie, seen him
second year, man. Seen him grow, watch
him grow. Um love it about him. love the
way he goes about his business and uh
man a chance to reunite with him, chance
to reunite with the coaching staff. I
could I couldn't pass it up. Uh man, we
have some unfinished business. I think
man, I know we're excited to go out here
and um do this. Germaine is a is a man a
heck of a football player. He's going to
give it all. He's going to play with
effort, technique, and violence. And I
do the same. And man, I'm excited to be
on the same team as him again.
Hey, this is Corey Curtis also with
News2 in Nashville and I'm I'm just
going to ask you a superficial easy
question. You you didn't wear the old
Titan uniform. What do you think of the
new one that you're you're walking into?
>> Man, I I think I came at the perfect
time. I tell you, I like this jersey a
lot. I think they did a great job
putting it together and uh man, I think
uh I hate to say I think I look the best
wearing it.
>> TD, go ahead.
Oops. I was on I was on mute. My bad.
You you saw when Salah came in and
established the culture there with the
Jets. Now, obviously, he's bringing you
here to Nashville to do the same. What
were some of the things that that you
saw before when he did that? And how the
conversations going as far as you being
a catalyst for that culture to be
installed here?
I think uh you know kind of the first
thing that stands out to me with Kosala
is is the speed in which we play and I
think it's amazing when uh you watch him
even talk about offense and you talk
about something as simple as catching
the ball and getting up field and you're
like man the noticeable change of speed
in which you play the physicality in
which even though there's two or three
guys in front of you you want to run
through them. Um, I think that, man, it
resonates throughout everybody. The
message is the same. And, uh, man, I
mean, it helps us play hard. It helps us
play violent. And I think that's half
the battle in the NFL. So, um, off the
top, I mean, I'm going to bring the
energy. I'm going to run. I'm going to
hit. I'm going to be physical. And, uh,
from there, I think the rest is going to
take care of itself for sure.
>> Okay, John. I think that's all all the
time we have. I appreciate your time.
Thank you.
>> In free agency and and when did you kind
of have a sense that Tennessee was was
going to be the spot for you?
>> My experience was good, you know, going
my first time going around. I was
talking to my agent Dave Muletta at
Athletes First and you know, he kept me
in the loop with, you know, the teams I
was talking to and the teams I
communicating with and um pretty much
just how it went. he just, you know, was
referring to me that I was, you know,
obviously communicated with the Giants
and Tennessee as well and that, you
know, it was in between the two of those
teams and, you know, I appreciate the
Giants giving me the opportunity, you
know, and to be there, but towards the
end of the process, we just felt like me
and my agent both, we felt like
Tennessee was the best fit for us.
>> Hey, Cordell Easton Freeze with a Toz
Sports. Um, the way that it was
reported, it sounds like there was kind
of a Hail Mary attempt there at the end
from Coach Salah talking to you about
what your role would be in this defense.
Is is that the way that it went down and
what was your role?
>> Sorry y'all went out. My bad. Uh, I
couldn't hear nothing actually after he
asked what my role was. Wi-Fi went out.
>> Can Can you hear me now, Cordell?
>> Yeah, I can hear you. My bad.
>> No, it's fine. Um, I was asking about
the way that it was reported. It It
sounded like Robert Salah called you
with kind of a a hailmary uh pitch there
at the end and and got you to to commit
to Tennessee by describing what your
role would be in this defense. Is that
the way that that it went down? And what
was that role?
>> Not necessarily. That wasn't the way it
really went down. I don't know where
they got that from to be honest. Uh but
pretty much it was just negotiation
within my agent and Salah. Obviously, I
knew that, you know, Salo interested in
me. He knew that, you know, build that
that field corner would be a good spot
for me in his defense. And, you know,
really just how I went was that last
call was just say, "Are you excited to
be a Titan?" And then we went from
there.
>> Paul.
>> Hey, Cordell. Paul Kuharski from Paul
Kuharski.com. Can you give us a scouting
report on you? And then can you give us
a scouting report on uh Wandale?
>> Scout report as in like, you know, what
I'm best at or scouting.
>> Tell us your game, the goods and the
bads, what you need to work on, and then
what it was like to cover. Uh maybe
Robinson during during training camp.
>> Yeah. Uh one deal he's a tough receiver
to cover first and foremost like you
know his game is different. He play
inside, he play outside. His case rate
is good. He got sure hands. He coming in
out his brakes and he also can out run
you. So playing with a guy now and being
with a guy like that competing you know
iron sharpens iron. So that was a good
way helping me sharpen myself at
practice. you know, he a shorter guy, so
it's hard to strong and, you know, so
it's hard to always get hands on because
he also physical as well at the point of
attack. So, he a receiver to me that can
pretty much do everything. I list him as
a top five receiver in this league. Me
personally, and um as far as my game,
I'm more of a technical corner, you
know, uh I ain't the biggest, but I like
to put my nose in and be feisty and
physical. I like to, you know, know what
the opposing offense want to attack me
like in the beginning of the games or to
start the game. Um, yeah, I just see
myself as a general in a quarterback
position. I'm not I can be hands, I can
press, I can do all those things. And
for myself personally, what I can feel
like I can work on, you know, as any
other corner work on is, you know,
attacking the ball, um, creating more
turnovers for this defense this year
and, you know, thriving from there.
>> Thanks,
>> TD.
>> Yeah, Cordell, what's up, man? Terron
Davenport, ESPN. Obviously, you know,
watching your your feisty style of play,
it's evidenced on on film, but what's
the mindset that you and Alante and Josh
Williams want to bring to the secondary
that's been revamped? And what are some
of the things specifically about Salah
and this defense that excite you about
this opportunity?
>> Yeah, I like solid defense is simple.
What I call it uh is like bread and
butter. You know what I'm saying? Like
we do the same things all the time, but
we perfecting to that craft. And so what
I like about Salah is just his
aggressiveness. You know what I'm
saying? Always, you know, just mixing
everything up. That's what I like about
Salah and his game. And I feel like me,
Alante, and Williams, we going, we plan
to be the best trio in the league. We
talked about it, you know, when we first
got together. We first shook hands on
the visit and we excited to work
together and beat them guys.
>> Teresa
>> Cordell, uh, welcome to town. uh in
looking at this defense, uh how much of
it was play this defense, have this
opportunity, play on a defense on the
back end with a Jeffrey Simmons up front
and how that helps you do your job.
>> Yeah, Jeffrey Simmons a dog. Of course,
I already knew about him before I got
over here just from watching film,
watching tape, and obviously that whole
front that they got here, Franklin
Myers, everybody. Germaine, it's going
to be good because it's going to put
pressure on the quarterback and that way
we can create turnovers and also the
quarterback not going to sit there and
have all the time in the world to be
able to throw the ball and when we
mixing up schemes and coverages, it's
going to make it harder for him to sit
there and, you know, look and find his
first option. So, I feel like with that
front, with the defense we got in here,
with the offense, Cam Ward and everybody
over there, feel like we gonna be
special this year.
>> Terry, go ahead.
Cordell, uh, when you signed here, a lot
of the reports said that you were an
ascending player, a guy maybe whose best
football still ahead of him. Do you feel
like that's accurate? And what do you
feel like your ceiling is as a football
player?
>> Yeah, I feel like that's accurate. Um, I
feel like that's what every player in
the league want to be. You know, nobody
want to, you know, stay in one spot when
they are trying to improve or be the
better version themselves. And for me,
it's just always about growth. Um, every
year I like to pick apart things I can
get better at or things that I may see
as a weakness on film and that's how I
just improve from there and try to be a
better version of myself out there on
the field for my teammates too.
>> Chris and then Nick.
>> Hey Cordell, it's Chris Harris at WSMV.
Um, just out of curiosity, what do you
believe uh, it takes to be a successful
member of the secondary in the NFL and
how does Robert Solah's defense kind of
play into that?
>> I believe it take leadership skills too,
you know, in the back end. Um, cuz with
the last line defense and, um, it's easy
to see when the back end is, you know,
not communicating off chemistry and
stuff like that. So, I feel like that's
what we got to, you know, hone in on
building camaraderie, the brotherhood as
a whole. But importantly as on the back
end and with solid defense, you know,
him being a defensive coach mindset too,
having Marco Emanuel that was also with
me at the Giants over and all those
other guys to be able to talk ball and
collaborate our ideas all together and
just to continue to grow. Right now we
all you know excited about the
opportunity but when OTAAS and
everything else start it's time to start
building that brotherhood and
camaraderie and start playing together
seeing how everybody will see the view
as a defense and working from there.
>> Hey Cordell nicks us at the Tennessee
and here in town um you mentioned all
the familiar faces coming from the
Giants from Daves on down. I was just
wondering can you speak to what the
culture was like in that organization?
Obviously, we didn't see a lot of wins,
a lot of onfield success, but there's so
many of you guys coming over here. Is
the plan to recreate what you guys did
there culturally? Is the plan to do
something different? Just how do you
speak to that?
>> Um, I'm sure the plan is to do something
different. Um, obviously, we didn't get
the result we wanted at the Giants when
we was there. Pretty much Carmen Day
ball one day, all this, I speak for us.
We didn't get the results we wanted, you
know, but we fought and the chrome ratio
over there was good and we had, you
know, the right guys in the locker room.
We had the right things going on. I just
feel like, you know, we couldn't put it
all together when it came to Sunday. And
so here at Tennessee, I'm sure we're
going to change it up. You know,
everywhere you want to find the best way
to win and that's what's going to be our
goal. Obviously, that's for the coaches,
you know, to figure out how they going
to do and go about things. But in the
locker room, I know the first start is
to create that brotherhood, create that
bond. That way, we want to compete for
each other and win games.
>> Okay, I think that's about it. Cordell,
I appreciate your time.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Thanks.